var quiztype = "c";


var questions = [{
	"question": "The C programming language is a?",
	"option1": "Assembly language",
	"option2": "Machine language",
	"option3": "High level language",
	"option4": "low level language",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Who invented the C language?",
	"option1": "Danis richie",
	"option2": "charls webbage",
	"option3": "john dalton",
	"option4": "None of the above",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "djfdfhdjkfdhkjfdfk?",
	"option1": "Gate",
	"option2": "Mother Board",
	"option3": "Chip",
	"option4": "CPU",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "C is ?",
	"option1": "A third generation high level language",
	"option2": "A machine language",
	"option3": "An assembly language",
	"option4": "All of the above",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Web pages are written using ?",
	"option1": "FTP",
	"option2": "HTTP",
	"option3": "HTML",
	"option4": "URL",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "UNIVAC is an example of",
	"option1": "First generation computer",
	"option2": "Second generation computer",
	"option3": "Third generation computer",
	"option4": "Fourth generation computer",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Which of the following is an example of non volatile memory ?",
	"option1": "VLSI",
	"option2": "LSI",
	"option3": "ROM",
	"option4": "RAM",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Graphic interfaces were first used in a xerox product is called ?",
	"option1": "Ethernet",
	"option2": "Inter LISP",
	"option3": "Small talk",
	"option4": "Zeta LISP",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Find the odd one out ?",
	"option1": "ORACLE",
	"option2": "SYBASE",
	"option3": "C",
	"option4": "INFORMIX",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "The ------ is the administrative section of the computer system?",
	"option1": "Memory Unit",
	"option2": "Input Unit",
	"option3": "Central Processing Unit",
	"option4": "Control Unit",
	"answer": "3"
}];